William N. Fenton Papers 1933-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.20
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1897-1994; 39 boxes; 19.25 linear feet
  - Mathews, Zena Pearlstone (Box Series I-22)
    -See Ser. I, Pearlstone, Zena
  - Mathur, Mary E. Fleming, 1969-1970 (Box Series I-22)
  - Maxon, S.A., 1943 (Box Series I-22)
    -See also Ser. I, Cornelius, Laura M.
  - Mayer, Stephan Karl, 1939-1940 (Box Series I-22)
  - Mead, Margaret, 1968-1977 (Box Series I-22)
    Metraux, Rhoda
  - Meade, Mary Jo, 1993 (Box Series I-22)
  - Medical Library Association, 1951 (Box Series I-22)
  - Medicine, Beatrice, 1986-1987 (Box Series I-22)
  - Mekeel, H. Scudder, 1936-1944 (Box Series I-22)
    -See also Ser. I, United States. Department of the Interior
  - Mele, Bette Crouse, 1963-1971 (Box Series I-22)
  - Meritt, B.D., 1948 (Box Series I-22)
    -See also Ser. I, Hamilton College
  - Meshejian, Haig C., 1945-1946 (Box Series I-22)
  - Metis Association of Alberta, 1986 (Box Series I-22)
  - Metraux, Alfred, 1947-1962 (Box Series I-22)
  - Metraux, Rhoda, 1968 (Box Series I-22)
    -See also Ser. I, Mead, Margaret
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1981 (Box Series I-22)
  - Metropolitan Toronto Library Board, 1985 (Box Series I-22)
  - Meyer, Roy W., 1968 (Box Series I-22)
  - Meyers, Jeffrey, 1993 (Box Series I-22)
  - Michael, Henry N., 1967 (Box Series I-22)
  - Michelson, Gunther, 1966, 1971-1992 (Box Series I-22)
  - Milbank, Tweed, Hadley & McCloy (Box Series I-22)
  - Milbourne, A. Virginia S., 1939-1940 (Box Series I-22)
    Stewart, Dale
  - Milwaukee Public Museum, 1940 (Box Series I-22)
  - Miller, David R., 1981-1994 (Box Series I-22)
  - Miller, P. Schuyler, 1971-1973 (Box Series I-22)
    -See also Ser. I, Lounsbury, Floyd G.
    -See also Ser. I, New York State Archaeological Association
  - Mimir Corporation, 1986 (Box Series I-22)
  - Miranda, José, 1960 (Box Series I-22)
  - Mitchell, Joseph, 1949 (Box Series I-22)
  - Mitchell, Mary Elizabeth, 1977 (Box Series I-22)
  - Mitchell Indian Museum, 1985-1986 (Box Series I-22)
  - Mochon, Donald, 1970 (Box Series I-22)
    Winkel, Nina
  - Modern Language Association of America, [197-] (Box Series I-22)
  - Moe, Henry Allen, 1966 (Box Series I-22)
  - Mohawk, John C., 1970 (Box Series I-22)
  - Mohawk Institute, 1972-1973, 1978 (Box Series I-22)
  - Momyer, George R., 1950 (Box Series I-22)
  - Montana State University, 1976 (Box Series I-22)
  - Monteith, Carmaleta L., 1985 (Box Series I-22)
  - Montgomery, Frances K., 1976 (Box Series I-22)
  - Montour, Ethel Brant, 1953 (Box Series I-22)
  - Monture, Phil, 1979 (Box Series I-22)
  - Moodie, Kathleen, 1943 (Box Series I-22)
  - Mook, Maurice, 1943-1944 (Box Series I-22)
  - Moore, Elizabeth Lowndes, 1952-1985 (Box Series I-22)
    Champlain Society
    Cross, Michael S.
  - Moorhead, M.J., 1980 (Box Series I-22)
    Bishop Museum
  - Moravian Church. Archives (Box Series I-22)
    -See Ser. I, The Archives of the Moravian Church
  - Morey, Sylvester M., 1960, 1970, 1974 (Box Series I-22)
  - Morgan, Arthur E., 1958-1961 (Box Series I-22)
    Abbett, Robert W.
    Itschner, Emerson C.
    Kennedy, John F.
  - Morgan, Edward A., 1980, 1989 (Box Series I-22)
  - Morgan, Ernest, 1961 (Box Series I-22)
  - Morgan, L.H. (Box Series I-22)
    -See Ser. I, Best, Elsdon
  - Morice, John H., 1940 (Box Series I-23)
  - Morin, Dolores, 1968 (Box Series I-23)
  - Morrell, William P., 1975-1976 (Box Series I-23)
  - Morris, C.P., 1974 (Box Series I-23)
  - Morris, Michèle R., 1986-1988 (Box Series I-23)
  - Morrison, Alvin Hamblen, 1966-1967, 1980 (Box Series I-23)
  - Morrow, W.C., 1944 (Box Series I-23)
  - William Morrow & Company, Inc., Publishers, 1950 (Box Series I-23)
  - Moses, Elliott, 1943-1958 (Box Series I-23)
  - Moses, Raymond D., 1935 (Box Series I-23)
  - Moss, Robert, 1987-1992 (Box Series I-23)
  - Mott, Austin L., III (Box Series I-23)
    -See Ser. I, Schine Queensbury Inn
  - Mount Pleasant, Robert, 1943 (Box Series I-23)
  - Mountford, C.P., 1945 (Box Series I-23)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick (Box Series I-23)
  - Mueller, Mariann B., 1969-1970 (Box Series I-23)
  - Muhlenberg College, 1975 (Box Series I-23)
    Francello, Joseph
  - Muller, Alexis V., Jr., 1952-1956, n.d. (Box Series I-23)
  - Munby, A.N.L., 1964 (Box Series I-23)
    -See also Ser. I, Ledden, Millie
  - Murdock, Charles C., 1991 (Box Series I-23)
  - Murdock, George Peter, 1940-1947, 1967 (Box Series I-23)
    -See also Ser. I, Society for Applied Anthropology
  - Murra, John, 1970-1971 (Box Series I-23)
  - Muser, Curt, 1992 (Box Series I-23)
  - Muser, Frani, 1987 (Box Series I-23)
  - Museum fur Volkerkunde (Box Series I-23)
    -See Ser. I, Staatliches Museum fur Volkerkunde
  - Museum of Mankind, 1980-1991 (Box Series I-23)
  - Museum of the American Indian (Box Series I-23)
    Abrams, George H.J.
    Abrams, Robert
    American Indian Community House
    Conable, Barber B., Jr.
    Coste, Ann R.
    Deloria, Vine, Jr.
    Draper, Alexander F.
    Ewers, John C.
    Glenbow Museum
    Hilton, D.B.
    Inouye, Daniel K.
    Institute of the American Indian and Alaska Native Culture and Arts Development
    Josephy, Alvin M., Jr.
    Kidd, Julie
    Metis Association of Alberta
    Milbank, Tweed, Hadley & McCloy
    Milwaukee Public Museum
    Morgan, Edward A.
    Moynihan, Daniel Patrick
    Muser, Curt
    National Congress of American Indians
    New York (City). Department of Cultural Affairs
    The New Yorker
    O'Malley, Cormac K.H.
    Ominayak, Bernard
    Oppenheimer-Nicolau, Siobhan
    O'Rorke, James F., Jr.
    Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison
    Powless, Irving, Jr.
    Rehnquist, William H.
    Roberts, Ann R.
    Roosevelt, Anna
    Shenandoah, Leon
    Smith, James G.E.
    Staatliches Museum Für Völkerkunde
    Sturtevant, William
    Swartz, Douglas W.
    Thomas, David Hurst
    U'Mista Central Centre
    Walsh, Martin W.
    Williams, John S., Jr.
    -See also Ser. I, Bachrach, Deborah
    -See also Ser. I, Cornplanter, Jesse
    -See also Ser. I, Ewers, John Canfield
    -See also Ser. I, Koch, Edward
    -See also Ser. I, Sturtevant, William
    -See also Ser. I, Williams, Paul
    -See also Ser. IV, Hatt, Robert T., "The Museum of the American Indian..."
    - *Folder #1, 1940-1976 (Box Series I-23)
    - Folder #2, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-23)
    - Folder #3, 1978-1979 (Box Series I-23)
    - Folder #4, 1980-1983 (Box Series I-23)
    - Folder #5, 1984 (Box Series I-23)
    - Folder #6, Jan.-Aug. 1985 (Box Series I-24)
    - Folder #7, Sep.-Dec. 1985 (Box Series I-24)
    - Folder #8, 1986-1987 (Box Series I-24)
    - Folder #9, Jan.-Sep. 1988 (Box Series I-24)
    - Folder #10, Oct. 1988-1994 (Box Series I-24)
  - Museum of the Cherokee Indian, 1949 (Box Series I-24)
  - Mussio, Laurence Basilio, 1988 (Box Series I-24)
  - Myers, Beatrice, 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - Myerson, Bess (Box Series I-24)
  - Mynter, Kenneth H., 1949-1950 (Box Series I-24)
    -See also Ser. I, Gabor, Robert
  - Myres, Sandra L., 1968 (Box Series I-24)
    Goodman, David
  - Namias, June, 1988 (Box Series I-25)
  - Namihira, Emiko, 1970 (Box Series I-25)
  - Napier, A. David, 1979 (Box Series I-25)
  - Naroll, Raoul, 1969 (Box Series I-25)
  - Nash, Philleo, 1961 (Box Series I-25)
  - National Cancer Institute, 1952 (Box Series I-25)
  - National Central Library, 1971 (Box Series I-25)
  - National Congress of American Indians (Box Series I-25)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1980-1988 (Box Series I-25)
  - National Film Board (Canada), 1945 (Box Series I-25)
    Grierson, John
  - National Geographic Society, 1968-1988 (Box Series I-25)
  - National Museum of Canada, 1933-1967 (Box Series I-25)
    Russell, Loris S.
    Jenness, Diamond
    -See also Ser. V, "Weapons: Bows, Arrows, Clubs"
  - National Museum of Man, 1971-1983 (Box Series I-25)
    Day, Gordan M.
    Dallaire, Louise
    -See also Ser. I, Canadian Museum of Civilization
  - National Museum of Natural Sciences (Canada), 1981 (Box Series I-25)
  - National Museum of Northern Ireland (Box Series I-25)
    -See Ser. I, Grand Council of the Crees (of Quebec)
  - National Museum of the American Indian (Box Series I-25)
  - National Research Council, 1945-1965 (Box Series I-25)
  - National Science Foundation, 1966-1970, 1987 (Box Series I-25)
  - Kenneth Nebenzahl, Inc., 1987 (Box Series I-25)
  - Neilson, Franz, 1942 (Box Series I-25)
  - The New Iroquois Indian Museum, 1994 (Box Series I-25)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1956 (Box Series I-25)
  - New York (City). Department of Cultural Affairs (Box Series I-25)
  - New York Community Trust, 1976 (Box Series I-25)
    Whelan, Sidney S., Jr.
  - New York Council for the Humanities, 1981-1982 (Box Series I-25)
  - New York Folklore Society, 1945, 1947 (Box Series I-25)
    Jones, Louis C.
    Thompson, Harold W.
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1964-1965 (Box Series I-25)
  - New-York Historical Society, 1944-1977 (Box Series I-25)
    Barck, Dorothy C.
    Vail, Robert W.G.
  - New York State Archaeological Association, 1940 (Box Series I-25)
  - New York (State). Comptroller, 1970 (Box Series I-25)
  - New York State Highway Department, 1936 (Box Series I-25)
  - New York State Historical Association, 1944-1988 (Box Series I-25)
  - New York State Library, 1944-1949, 1979 (Box Series I-25)
    Vail, [Robert] W.G.
  - New York State Museum (Box Series I-26)
    Gillette, Charles E.
    Hamell, George R.
    Sullivan, Martin
    -See also Ser. I, Ninham, Fred
    -See also Ser. I, Whitney, Alvin
    - Folder #1, 1932-1960 (Box Series I-26)
    - Folder #2, 1961-1987 (Box Series I-26)
    - Folder #3, 1988-1994 (Box Series I-26)
  - New York Times, 1971-1972, 1992 (Box Series I-26)
  - The New Yorker (Box Series I-26)
  - New Zealand Consulate-General, 1977 (Box Series I-26)
  - New Zealand-United States Educational Foundation, 1974-1975, 1978, 1988 (Box Series I-26)
  - Newberry Library, 1952-1993 (Box Series I-26)
    Hoxie, Frederick E.
    Trout, Lawana
  - Newcombe, David S., 1969 (Box Series I-26)
  - Newhouse, Seth (Box Series I-26)
  - Newman, Marshall T., 1957 (Box Series I-26)
  - Newton, Dolores, 1972, 1977 (Box Series I-26)
  - Nicholas, Ralph W., 1958 (Box Series I-26)
  - Nichols, John R. (Box Series I-26)
    -See Ser. I, Cohen, Felix S.
    -See Ser. I, United States. Department of the Interior
  - Nichols, Phebe Jewell (Box Series I-26)
    -See Ser. I, Lookaround, Angus F. (Mrs.)
  - Nickerson, Gifford S., 1969 (Box Series I-26)
  - Ninham, Fred, 1950 (Box Series I-26)
    New York State Museum
  - Nitsch, Twylah, 1969 (Box Series I-26)
  - Nixon, Howard L. II, 1972 (Box Series I-26)
  - Noakes, G. Thomas, 1991 (Box Series I-26)
    Bogyi, A.M.
  - Noble, Bill, [1969] (Box Series I-26)
  - Noon, John A., 1941-1945 (Box Series I-26)
    Embree, John F.
    -See also Ser. I, Lindsey, Edward
  - Norbeck, Edward, 1969 (Box Series I-26)
  - Northeast Indian Quarterly, 1989 (Box Series I-26)
  - Northwestern University, 1947 (Box Series I-26)
  - W.W. Norton and Company, Inc., 1979 (Box Series I-26)
  - Nurge, Ethel, 1973 (Box Series I-26)
  - Nyquist, E.B., 1957 (Box Series I-26)
  - O'Brien, Leo W., 1957, 1962 (Box Series I-26)
  - Oddon, Yvonne, 1956 (Box Series I-26)
  - O'Donnell, Thomas F., 1968 (Box Series I-26)
  - Oehser, Paul H., 1954-1988, n.d. (Box Series I-26)
    Crossette, George
    Stanley, R.W.
    -See also Ser. I, Cosmos Club
  - Oestreich, Nancy (Box Series I-26)
    -See Ser. I, Lurie, Nancy Oestreich
  - Oestreicher, David, 1994 (Box Series I-26)
  - Oheyohnoh, 1979, 1984 (Box Series I-26)
  - Olbrechts, Frans M., 1937, 1939 (Box Series I-26)
  - Olde, Evelyn, 1985-1985 (Box Series I-26)
  - Olderogge, D.A., 1964-1965 (Box Series I-26)
  - O'Leary, Dillon, 1970 (Box Series I-26)
  - Olien, Michael D., 1969 (Box Series I-26)
  - O'Malley, Cormac K.H. (Box Series I-26)
  - Ominayak, Bernard, 1986-1987 (Box Series I-26)
    International Workgroup for Indigenous Affairs
  - Oneida Historical Society, 1974 (Box Series I-27)
  - Oneida Indian Nation, 1993-1994 (Box Series I-27)
  - Oneida Tribe of Indians of Wisconsin, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box Series I-27)
  - O'Neill, Edward E. (Box Series I-27)
    Smyser, R.E., Jr.
    - Folder #1, 1957-1958 (Box Series I-27)
    - Folder #2, 1959-1960 (Box Series I-27)
  - Onondaga Historical Association, 1945-1949, 1970 (Box Series I-27)
  - Onondaga Nation, 1986 (Box Series I-27)
  - Ontario County Historical Society, 1949 (Box Series I-27)
  - Opler, Morris Edward, 1946-1949, 1962 (Box Series I-27)
  - Oppenheimer-Nicolau, Siobhan (Box Series I-27)
  - O'Reilly, Susan McLeod, 1982 (Box Series I-27)
  - Orenstein, Henry, 1968 (Box Series I-27)
  - O'Rorke, James F., Jr. (Box Series I-27)
  - Osgood, Cornelius B., 1946-1965 (Box Series I-27)
  - Osmolskis, Tadas, 1968 (Box Series I-27)
  - Ostertag, Harold C., 1957 (Box Series I-27)
  - Ottery, Faith, 1972-1973 (Box Series I-27)
  - Otto, Karl, 1968 (Box Series I-27)
  - Owen, Benjamin Daniel, 1991-1992 (Box Series I-27)
  - Owl, Della Brunsteter, 1947 (Box Series I-27)
  - Owl, Frell, 1978 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pacific Historical Review, 1973 (Box Series I-27)
  - Painter, Levinus K., 1966 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pandey, Triloki Nath, 1968-1984 (Box Series I-27)
  - Paolillo, Susan, 1970 (Box Series I-27)
  - Paonessa, Rose E., 1971 (Box Series I-27)
  - Paredes, J. Anthony, 1972 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pariser, Diane, 1974, 1980 (Box Series I-27)
  - Parker, Arthur C., 1908-1951 (Box Series I-27)
    Hauck, Mary Barnum Bush
    -See also Ser. I, Hogg, David A.
  - Parker, Dorothy R., 1987 (Box Series I-27)
  - Parker, Jimmy B., 1972 (Box Series I-27)
  - Parker, Judy (Box Series I-27)
  - Parkhurst, George V., 1948 (Box Series I-27)
  - Parks, Douglas R., 1990 (Box Series I-27)
  - Parsegian, V. Larry, 1970 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pasel, Gladys, 1949 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pasztory, Esther, 1979 (Box Series I-27)
  - Patterson, Phoebe, 1943 (Box Series I-27)
  - Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison (Box Series I-27)
  - Payne, Helen Canfield, 1974 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pearce, Roy Harvey, 1944-1945, 1953 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pearlstone, Zena, 1973-1987 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pechuman, LaVerne, 1968 (Box Series I-27)
  - Peck, John (Box Series I-27)
    -See Ser. I, Farrar, Straus & Giroux, Inc.
  - Peckham, Howard H., 1960 (Box Series I-27)
  - Peek Publications, 1982 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pendergast, James F., 1972-1991 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pennsylvania Historical Association, 1987 (Box Series I-27)
  - Pennsylvania Historical Commission, 1941-1979 (Box Series I-27)
    Cadzow, Donald A.
    Kent, Donald H.
    Stevens, S.K.
  - Pennsylvania Parks Association, 1945 (Box Series I-27)
    Chapman, Ellwood B.
  - Pettinos, Emily, 1966-1967 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pettit, P.B., 1949 (Box Series I-28)
  - Phalen, Ann Marie Powers, 1970-1976 (Box Series I-28)
  - Philadelphia Anthropological Society, 1942 (Box Series I-28)
  - Philipson, Morris (Box Series I-28)
    -See Ser. I, Gray, John M.
  - Phillips, Annette, 1982 (Box Series I-28)
  - Phillips, Edward Hake, 1949, 1967 (Box Series I-28)
  - Phillips, Wendell, 1945, 1971 (Box Series I-28)
  - Phillips Academy, 1901-1902 (Box Series I-28)
  - Phinney, John F.S., 1972 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pickering, John, 1949 (Box Series I-28)
  - Piepkorn, Arthur Carl, 1968, 1972 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pierce, Clinton G., 1964, 1967 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pierce, Germaine Kettle, 1958 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pierly, Caroline, 1946 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pike, Robert E., 1943 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pilant, Richard, 1958-1962 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pilette, Marie-Laure, 1987 (Box Series I-28)
    -See also Ser. I, Simonis, Yvan
  - Piper, Raymond F., 1950 (Box Series I-28)
  - Piskor, Frank, 1979 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pitt Rivers Museum, 1943, 1970 (Box Series I-28)
    -See also Ser. I, Blackwood, Beatrice
    -See also Ser. I, Fagg, Bernard
  - Placak, Joe C., Jr., 1971 (Box Series I-28)
  - Plant, Christopher H., 1976 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pleck, Elizabeth, 1985 (Box Series I-28)
  - Plum, Dorothy A. (Box Series I-28)
    -See Ser. I, Vassar College Library
  - Plummer, Genevieve R., 1970 (Box Series I-28)
  - Plummer, Sanford W., 1946 (Box Series I-28)
  - Plunz, Richard A., 1985 (Box Series I-28)
  - Poleman, Horace, 1945, n.d. (Box Series I-28)
  - Pollenz, Philippa, 1943-1948 (Box Series I-28)
  - Polsky, Richard M., 1980-1981 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pond, Joe, 1969 (Box Series I-28)
  - Poodry, Alice M., 1946 (Box Series I-28)
  - Porter, Joy, 1992 (Box Series I-28)
  - Post, C. Gordan, 1969 (Box Series I-28)
  - Postlethwaite, Gayton, 1940 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pouliot, Léon, 1940-1979 (Box Series I-28)
    Lamalle, Edmond
  - Pouwer, Jan, 1975 (Box Series I-28)
  - Powdermaker, Hortense, 1948 (Box Series I-28)
  - Powell, Peter S., 1969 (Box Series I-28)
  - Power, Boyd D., 1989 (Box Series I-28)
  - Powers, Alfred, 1944 (Box Series I-28)
  - Powers, Ann Marie (Box Series I-28)
    -See Ser. I, Phalen, Ann Marie Powers
  - Powers, Frederick, 1968, 1977 (Box Series I-28)
  - Powers, Mabel, 1946-1947 (Box Series I-28)
  - Powless, Irving, Jr., 1971 (Box Series I-28)
  - Frederick A. Praeger, Inc., 1970 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pratt, Frederick H., 1949-1950 (Box Series I-28)
  - Presnall, Clifford C., 1943 (Box Series I-28)
  - Preston, Jack, 1961, n.d. (Box Series I-28)
  - Preston, Richard J., 1970-1984 (Box Series I-28)
  - Price, John A., 1979-1980 (Box Series I-28)
  - Priestley, E.J. (Box Series I-28)
  - Priestman, Keith B. (Box Series I-28)
  - Princeton University Press, 1972 (Box Series I-28)
  - Printup, Maribel (Box Series I-28)
  - Printup, Shirley W. (Box Series I-28)
    -See Ser. I, Vanatta, Shirley W. Printup
  - Printup, Wayne (Box Series I-28)
  - Probe, 1967 (Box Series I-28)
  - Prucha, John James, 1974 (Box Series I-28)
  - Pryor, Frederic L., 1974 (Box Series I-28)
  - Quain, Buell, n.d. (Box Series I-28)
  - Quinn, David B., 1984 (Box Series I-28)
  - Radin, Paul, 1959 (Box Series I-28)
  - Raemsch, Bruce E., 1965, 1968 (Box Series I-28)
  - Ragsdale, James, 1978, 1981 (Box Series I-28)
  - Rainey, Froelich G., 1948-1974 (Box Series I-28)
  - Rainsford, Helen Morgan, 1968 (Box Series I-28)
  - Rakove, Jack N., 1984 (Box Series I-28)
  - Randall, Bette, 1977 (Box Series I-28)
  - Randle, E.P., 1945-1948 (Box Series I-28)
  - Randle, Martha Champion, 1937-1954 (Box Series I-28)
    -See also Ser. I, Lucy, Charles L.
  - Random House, Inc., 1972 (Box Series I-28)
    Leacock, Eleanor Burke
  - Raphael, Elizabeth, 1965 (Box Series I-28)
  - Rapp, Marvin, 1990 (Box Series I-28)
  - Ray, Verne F., 1945 (Box Series I-28)
    -See also Ser. I, Mandelbaum, David
  - Reaman, G.E., 1941 (Box Series I-29)
  - Redeye, Clara, 1934-1972 (Box Series I-29)
    -See also Ser. I, Redeye, Sherman
  - Redeye, Sherman, 1933-1946 (Box Series I-29)
    Fenton, John William
    Red Thunder Cloud, Chief
    -See Ser. I, Westez, Carlos
  - Reed, Daniel A. (Box Series I-29)
  - Reedy, James, 1970 (Box Series I-29)
  - Regan, Emmett W., 1942 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rehder, Harald A., 1949 (Box Series I-29)
    -See also Ser. I, Allard, H.A.
  - Rehnquist, William H. (Box Series I-29)
  - Reiff, Harry, 1948 (Box Series I-29)
  - Reilly, Joseph M., 1970 (Box Series I-29)
    -See also Ser. I, Hudacs, John
  - Reilly, Paul G., 1950-1954, 1968 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rementer, Jim, 1993 (Box Series I-29)
  - Reporter (Box Series I-29)
  - RESA, 1950 (Box Series I-29)
  - Research Publications, 1984 (Box Series I-29)
  - Reyes, Eleanor J., 1986 (Box Series I-29)
  - Reynolds, Barrie, 1970-1972 (Box Series I-29)
  - Reynolds, Margaret, 1943 (Box Series I-29)
  - Reynolds, Sam, 1970 (Box Series I-29)
  - Richards, H. Ames, Jr., 1971 (Box Series I-29)
  - Richardson, Miles, 1970, 1973 (Box Series I-29)
  - Richling, Barnett, 1988-1989 (Box Series I-29)
  - Richter, Daniel K., 1985-1993 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rickert, Shirley Kassman, 1970 (Box Series I-29)
  - Ridenour, W.E., 1943 (Box Series I-29)
  - Ridge, Martin, 1981 (Box Series I-29)
  - Ridley, Frank, 1978 (Box Series I-29)
  - Riegelman, Strasser and Spiegelberg, 1954 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rinkus, Louis P., 1964 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rioux, Marcel, 1950-1951 (Box Series I-29)
  - Ripken, Henry E. (Mrs.) (Box Series I-29)
  - Ripley, Scott, 1971 (Box Series I-29)
  - Ripley, S. Dillon, 1963-1964 (Box Series I-29)
  - Riposo, Nancy, 1973 (Box Series I-29)
    Lindsay, G. Carroll
  - Risley, Marius, 1941 (Box Series I-29)
  - Ritchie, William A., 1939-1970 (Box Series I-29)
    -See also Ser. I, Seneca Nation of Indians
    -See also Ser. I, Thiel, Barbara
  - Ritzenthaler, Robert, 1968-1970 (Box Series I-29)
  - Robb, Wallace Havelock, 1943-1944 (Box Series I-29)
  - Robbins, Clyde (Box Series I-29)
  - Roberge, Marti, 1982 (Box Series I-29)
  - Roberts, Ann R. (Box Series I-29)
  - Roberts, David, 1945 (Box Series I-29)
  - Roberts, Frank H.H., Jr., 1948 (Box Series I-29)
    Tatum, Robert M.
  - Roberts, Helen H., 1941 (Box Series I-29)
  - Roberts, John M., 1960, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-29)
  - Roberts, R.B., 1940 (Box Series I-29)
  - Robie, Harry, 1968, 1982 (Box Series I-29)
  - Robinson, Percy J., 1945-1949 (Box Series I-29)
  - Robinson, Roy H., 1969 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rochester Museum and Science Center, 1968-1991 (Box Series I-29)
    Collamer, Jeanette R.
    Syracuse University Press
    Thomas, W. Stephen
    -See also Ser. I, Collamer, Jeanette R.
  - Rochester Museum of Arts and Sciences, 1936-1955 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1944-1971 (Box Series I-29)
    -See also Ser. I, Marshall, Alton G.
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1944, 1971 (Box Series I-29)
    Marshall, John
    Stevens, David H.
  - Rockwell, William Walker, 1949 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rogers, Edward S., 1966, 1972-1973 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rogow, Sally, 1953 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rokusek, Robert J., 1987 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rolle, Andrew, 1992 (Box Series I-29)
  - Romero, Janice, 1980-1981, 1994 (Box Series I-29)
  - Roosevelt, Anna Curtenius, 1988 (Box Series I-29)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box Series I-29)
    -See Ser. I, Hauptman, Laurence Marc
  - Roseberry, [Cecil R.] "Tip", [1970] (Box Series I-29)
  - Rosen, Joseph, 1941 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rosenthal, Beryl, 1982 (Box Series I-29)
  - Rothenberg, Diane, 1979, 1985-1987 (Box Series I-30)
  - Rotstein, Abe, 1969-1970 (Box Series I-30)
  - Round Dance Productions, 1993 (Box Series I-30)
  - Rouse, Irving, 1945-1946, 1967, 1969 (Box Series I-30)
  - Rousseau, Jacques, 1945-1970 (Box Series I-30)
  - Rowell, Mary King (Box Series I-30)
    -See Ser. I, Carse, Mary King Rowell
  - Roy, Edouard, 1939 (Box Series I-30)
  - Royal Anthropological Institute, 1949-1953 (Box Series I-30)
  - Royal Canadian Institute, 1945-1946 (Box Series I-30)
  - Royal Ontario Museum, 1940, 1969-1989 (Box Series I-30)
  - Rubey, William W. (Box Series I-30)
    -See Ser. I, Lurie, Edward
  - Rugg, Harold G. (Box Series I-30)
  - Russell, Eber L., 1939, 1954 (Box Series I-30)
  - Russell, Loris S., 1962 (Box Series I-30)
    -See also Ser. I, National Museum of Canada
  - Rutherford, Walter D., 1958-1980 (Box Series I-30)
  - Ruthman, Elisabeth, 1988 (Box Series I-30)
  - Ryan, Allan J., 1987 (Box Series I-30)
  - Sacca, Harriet W., 1981 (Box Series I-30)
  - St. Hilaire, George, 1974 (Box Series I-30)
  - St. Lawrence University, 1938, 1972-1976 (Box Series I-30)
  - Saint Peter's Church, 1963, 1967 (Box Series I-30)
  - San Diego Museum of Man (Box Series I-30)
    -See Ser. I, Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anthropological Research
  - Sano, Chiyeko, 1970 (Box Series I-30)
  - Sapir, Edward, 1934-1938 (Box Series I-30)
    -See also Ser. I, Brock, R.W.
    -See also Ser. I, Goldenweiser, Alexander A.
    -See also Ser. I, Waugh, F.W.
  - Sapir, Jean, 1939 (Box Series I-30)